commercialsearch.com 2016-03-14

# Privacy Policy - commercialsearch.com

Xceligent takes your privacy very seriously. This statement discloses the privacy practices for the CommercialSearch website, located at www.commercialsearch.com (the "Site"). By using the Site you agree to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this statement.

BY USING THE SITE, YOU AGREE TO OUR COLLECTION, USE AND MAINTENANCE OF YOUR INFORMATION IN THE UNITED STATES. 

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Statement, please send us an [e-mail](mailto:info@xceligent.com) or contact us by mail at 4231 S. Hocker Drive, Building 13, Independence, MO 64055.

### Collection of Information

We collect information from you when you submit an online inquiry or create an account. This information may include name, e-mail address, phone and postal address. We also aggregate information related to the pages consumers view when they visit our site. We use this information to respond to your inquiry, provide you with information about products and services, and to identify your visits to available properties in the Site. We may also collect contact and other information from you if you subscribe to any of our services or otherwise voluntarily submit information to us.

You always have the ability to opt out of receiving future mailings and special offers; see the "Opt Out" section below.

As part of the standard operation of the Site, we may collect certain non-personal information from you, including but not limited to your browser type, operating system, IP address and the domain name from which you accessed the Site. In addition, we may collect information about your browsing behavior, such as the date and time you visit the Site, the areas or pages of the Site that you visit, the amount of time you spend viewing the Site, the number of times you return to the Site and other click-stream data. We do not combine this non-personal information with your personal information. We use this information to: (1) administer the Site, monitor its usage and diagnose problems with it; (2) remember you when you return to the Site, so that you don't have to re-submit information and preferences; and (3) conduct research to improve our content and services.

We use web beacons, which are tiny graphic images, in our e-mails. These help us measure the effectiveness of our e-mail campaigns, by telling us whether the messages have been received, opened or otherwise acted upon.

### Information Use

We may use the information we collect from and about you for any of the following purposes: (1) to fulfill your requests for products and services; (2) to provide you with targeted offers, Site content and advertising on the Site; (3) to contact you with information and promotional materials and offers from our company if you have agreed to receive such communications; (4) to contact you when necessary; (5) to review Site and product usage and operations; (6) to identify your display of a property detail page to the listing broker; (7) address problems with the Site, our business or our products and services; and (8) to protect the security or integrity of the Site and our business. 

### Information Disclosure

We may disclose the information collected from and about you as follows: (1) to our service providers, who may use it only on our behalf; (2) as necessary, if we believe that there has been a violation of our Site Terms of Use or of our rights or the rights of any third party; (3) to respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law; (4) to our affiliates; (5) to users who have listings in the Site; and (6) as disclosed to you at the point of collection. In addition, if our company or substantially all of its assets are acquired, your personal information may be one of the transferred assets.

We may share aggregate, non-personally identifiable information about you with third parties for research and other purposes.

### Opt Out

You may opt out of receiving future communications by following the instructions in each e-mail you may receive.

### Access

To access, correct or request that we make no further use of your personal information, please send us an e-mail at [info@xceligent.com](mailto:info@xceligent.com) or contact us by mail at 4231 S. Hocker Drive, Building 13, Independence, MO 64055.

### Security

Xceligent has taken certain physical, electronic, contractual and managerial steps to safeguard and secure your personal information. It is your responsibility to maintain the confidentiality of your Site account information, including your password, and you are responsible for all use of the Site accessed through it. You agree to notify us immediately of any unauthorized use of your account or any other actual or suspected breach of Site security.

### Changes to this Privacy Statement

We may change this Privacy Statement from time to time. When we do, we will post the change(s) on the Site. If we change the statement in a material way, we will provide appropriate online notice to you.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, the practices of the Site, or dealings with the Site or with us, contact:

Brand Director for CommercialSearch  
Xceligent, Inc.  
4231 S. Hocker Drive, Building 13  
Independence, MO 64055  
Phone: (877) 628-5300
